israelbiblicalstudies.com 2019-05-31

# Privacy Policy - Israel Institute of Biblical Studies

This Privacy Policy (the “Privacy Policy”) contains information regarding our privacy policy and practice and is brought to you so you feel comfortable using our website and services. It is presented for your benefit and describes how we collect and use information. Please take a minute to read the following statement in order to make sure you agree with our practices. By using the Israel Institute of Biblical Studies website located at https://israelbiblicalstudies.com and/or its subdomains, web properties and services available thereon (collectively, the “Site”), you permit the usage of your Personal Information (the term as such is defined below) as outlined below in our Privacy Policy and in the Terms of Use. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not access or otherwise use this Site.

The Site is owned and operated by eTeacher Ltd. (“eTeacher”, “we”, “us” or “our”). The Site is hosted by a third party providing hosting services to eTeacher, and eTeacher does not host the Site by itself. Therefore, information we collect from you or that you provide us with is hosted on servers owned and controlled by such third parties, hosting services providers. These servers may be located in different locations worldwide, and your information may be replicated across several servers in different locations worldwide. By consenting to the provisions of this Privacy Policy you are also consenting to such information being transferred to various third parties’ servers worldwide.

The headlines used in this Privacy Policy are for convenience only and shall not be used for any other purposes, including for the construction or interpretation of any provision of this Privacy Policy.

 **Terms of Use  
**This Privacy Policy forms part of the Site’s general terms of use which can be found here: https://israelbiblicalstudies.com/terms-of-use/ (“Terms of Use”), and should be read together with the Terms of Use, as it may be updated from time to time.

 **Collection of Information  
**We highly respect your privacy and take special measures to ensure that any personal information collected by us is used solely in accordance with our Privacy Policy. It is important for us that you understand both what kind of information is collected and how it is used.  
As part of the services granted by the Site, people using the Site may leave their private details on our registration form. We will not share this information with any non-affiliated third parties unless you specify otherwise.

 **Collection of Information; Type of Information Collected**

Information may be collected in any of the following ways:

  1.  _Information you provide us with_

At the outset of joining the services provided on the Site, you may be prompted to provide certain contact information, in order for us to be able to identify and/or contact you regarding our services and/or products. Such prompted information may include your first and last name, mailing address, e-mail address, phone number, Instant Messenger ID, and certain location information such as city, state, and/or zip code, as well as other necessary contact related information (“Personal Information”). For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, the term “Personal Information” means information that may be used either alone or in combination with other information, to personally identify an individual (as detailed in this section). Please note that you are not legally obligated to provide us with your Personal Information, and you acknowledge that providing us with your Personal Information is done by your own free will.

Here are some examples of information you may be required to provide us with when using the Site:

  * “Contact Us” link. If you choose to send us an inquiry using the “Contact us” link on the Site, whether by submitting our online form, by using a feedback or reporting feature on the site, by sending us an e-mail or by any other means, you may be required to provide certain Personal Information such as a full name, phone number and e-mail address.

  * Surveys, Promotions, Blogs and Newsletters. The Site may offer you certain features such as a blog, forums, newsletters, articles, reviews, surveys, etc. If you choose to subscribe to our newsletter, and/or to participate in a certain survey and/or to respond on the blog forum and/or participate in other promotional features offered by the Site (some of which may be administrated by third parties engaged by us), then such interaction by you may require you to provide certain Personal Information such as full name, phone number, physical address and e-mail address.

  2. Information We Collect from You

Kindly note that Personal Information may also include certain information which is not explicitly submitted by you, for example, as we log your browser-type related information, IP address, requested URL, referring URL, and timestamp.

Information, including Personal Information, is collected from you in the following ways:

  * Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies. The Site may use “Cookies” and other tracking services such as “web beacons” and pixel tags”. Upon your first visit to the Site, a “cookie” is sent to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. A “cookie” is a small file containing a string of characters that is sent to your computer when you visit a website and is stored by your browser. Some of the cookies are set by eTeacher, however some may be set by third parties. Cookies cause no harm to your computer or to your web browsing experience; on the contrary, we use cookies and other tracking technologies to improve the quality of our service, to improve the user experience of the Site, to monitor our servers, to better understand how people interact with us (for example, by collecting statistical data about how you and other users interact and use the Site) and to provide you with advertisements. Please also note that our advertisers may also place or recognize cookies on your browsers.

You may delete cookies that have been set on your computer and/or change your browser settings in order to block cookies or to receive notifications when cookies are set. For more information, please consult your browser settings. Please note that if you choose to restrict or block cookies on your browser, you will still be able to use our Site, however, several features offered on the Site may not be available to you.

  * Device and Usage Data; Log Files. We collect information through server log files and tracking technologies within the Site. Such information is collected for the purpose of tracking user movement around the Site and user clicks-through other websites, gathering demographic information, analyzing trends, and to generally collect information that we may find insightful or helpful. Such information may, without limitation, include the following: IP and Mac addresses, the type of your browser, operating system and device, your browser version, screen resolution, user agent, language and identifier, URLs and traffic channels (such as the previous URLs or platforms you visited), keyword searches and bids, city, region code, country, latitude, gender, age, date/time stamp of Site use, Internet Service Provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, clicks, timing and statistical data for clicks and page views, and clicked pages. For example, our Site uses Google Analytics service (more information regarding such service can be found on: <https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/partners/>).

By consenting to this Privacy Policy, you acknowledge that the information from you, as described in this sub-section titled “Information We Collect from You”, may also be used by third parties (as detailed in this Sub-Section) which may have their own privacy policies which are not necessarily adhere to this Privacy Policy.

Please note that any content that you choose to make publicly available on or via the Site, will be available to other users of the Site. We therefore encourage you to only post information you wish to be publicly available to other users of the Site’s third parties. If you allow your contact information to be public, you may receive unsolicited messages or activity from other users of the Site outside our control.

 **Use of Personal Information**

In addition to the uses of the Personal Information as detailed in this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use, we also make the following use of the Personal Information:

  1. To provide you with the Site and the services and features offered by the Site. We will use your Personal Information to: (a) administer and provide you with the Site, including the services and features offered by the Site; (b) identify and/or authenticate your access and use of the Site; (c) send you updates, newsletters, marketing materials (including that of third parties), offerings, advertisements and/or other information about the Site and/or eTeacher and/or its affiliates and business partners; (d) further develop, upgrade and improve the Site and its features; (e) communicate with you.

  2. Sharing Personal Information with Third Parties. We may share your Personal Information with certain third parties we engage with in order to improve the Site and user experience, to better understand how our users use the Site and to assist us with our business operations (for example, email administration providers and customer service operators). As previously stated in this Privacy Policy, these third parties and their servers may be located in different locations worldwide and may have their own privacy policies (if at all) which do not necessarily adhere to this Privacy Policy; however, we do try to engage third parties that have a privacy policy, including these third parties.

  3. Sharing Personal Information with Affiliates and Business Partners. We may share your Personal Information with our affiliated entities and/or business partners worldwide for processing needs and for the purpose of storing such information on our behalf. We require these affiliated entities and business partners to agree to process Personal Information in accordance with the provisions of this Privacy Policy.

  4. If Required by Law Enforcement. We may share your Personal Information with third parties if we believe, in our sole and absolute discretion, that the disclosure of such information to third parties is reasonably required, necessary and/or helpful to: (a) comply with any applicable law or regulation, legal proceeding, decree, or in response to a governmental authority request; (b) investigate a possible violation of our Terms of Service and/or in order to enforce its terms; (c) investigate and prevent security or fraud issues related to the Site; and (d) protect from any violation or threatened violation of our (or our affiliates and business partners), our users, yourself and/or the public’s rights, assets and safety.

 **Security of Information  
**As we are committed to protecting the security of your Personal Information, we use various security technologies and means (administrative, physical and technical) in order to help protect your Personal Information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. However, while we try to use reasonably acceptable means to protect your Personal Information from unauthorized use or access, we cannot guarantee its absolute confidentiality or security.

 **Correcting or Deleting Personal Information  
**We strive to maintain accurate records of Personal Information. If you are interested in correcting or deleting the Personal Information we may be storing, you may do so by contacting us at: contact@israelbiblicalstudies.com to request the correction or deletion of your Personal Information. Information deleted by you, or pursuant to a request you submitted to us may not necessarily be deleted permanently and may still remain stored on our servers. We reserve the right, in our sole and absolute discretion, to decide if such information is deleted from our servers permanently.

 **Unsubscribe  
**You may choose not to receive future emails, marketing materials, offers, etc. from us, by clicking on the “Remove me from mailing list” button located on the bottom of each e-mail we send you. However, if you choose to unsubscribe, we still may send you administrative e-mails in order to facilitate your use of the Site and the services and features offered by it.

 **Links to Other Websites  
**Our Site may contain links to third party websites, content and other online properties (“Third Party Websites”). Any data and/or Personal Information you provide in such Third Party Websites is provided at your own risk. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of these Third Party Websites, nor will we be liable for any content related claim arising from visiting such Third Party Websites, and we encourage you to read the terms and conditions and privacy policies of each Third Party Website you choose to use or interact with.

 **Privacy of Children  
**This Site is not designed to attract or to be used and/or accessed by children under the age of 13. Accordingly, we do not intend to collect Personal Information from anyone we know to be under the age of 13. If we learn that we have collected Personal Information from a child under the age of 13, we will use commercially reasonable efforts to delete such information as soon as practically possible. If you believe that we might have any such information, please contact us at contact@israelbiblicalstudies.com.

 **Changes to Privacy Policy  
**We reserve the right, in our sole and absolute discretion, to update and/or make changes to this Privacy Policy at any time. When we make these updates and/or changes, we will post the revised Privacy Policy on the Site and will post a prominent notice to that regard on the Site’s home page, and the “last updated” date listed at the top of this Privacy Policy will be changed accordingly. Your continuous use of the Site following such a post shall be deemed as your consent to the terms of the revised Privacy Policy.

 **California Specific Privacy Rights  
**Pursuant to the California Civil Code Section 1798.83, our customers who are California residents are permitted to request certain information regarding our disclosure of Personal Information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. If you wish to submit such a request, please send an email to contact@israelbiblicalstudies.com. Please note that we are only required to respond to one request per customer, each year.

 **California “Do Not Track” (DNT) Signals  
**We do not currently respond or take any action with respect to web browsers’ “do not track” (DNT) signals or other tools providing users with the ability to exercise choice regarding the collection of Personal Information about their online activities over time and across third-party web sites and/or online services. We may allow third parties, such as third parties providing us with analytics tools services, to collect Personal Information about an individual user’s online activities over time and across different web sites and services when a user uses our Site.

 **Removal of Content Published by California Residents  
**If you are a California resident under the age of 18 years old, the California Business and Professions Code Section 22581 may permit you to remove content or information you have publicly posted on our Site. If you wish to remove such content or information from our Site and you specify which content or information you wish to be removed from our Site, we will do so in accordance with applicable law. However, please note that after removal of such content from our Site you will not be able to restore such information. In addition, such removal does not ensure complete or comprehensive removal of the content or information you have posted on our Site and there may be circumstances in which the applicable law does not require us to enable removal of the content or information.

 **Assignment upon Merger or Sale; Receivership  
**In the event that eTeacher is acquired by, or merged with, a third party entity, or otherwise sells all, or part of its assets, we may (and hereby reserve the right to) transfer or assign the Personal Information and other information we have collected or received. Please note that in the event of a bankruptcy, insolvency, receivership, or similar event, we may not necessarily be able to control how your Personal Information is used, treated or transferred.

 **Privacy-Related Inquiries and Complaints  
**If you believe that we have not complied with this Privacy Policy with respect to your Personal Information or if you have other related comments, inquiries or concerns, please feel free to write us at: contact@israelbiblicalstudies.com.

 **Governing Law  
**This Privacy Policy shall be governed by and interpreted in accordance with the laws of the State of Israel, without giving effect to its conflict of the law’s provisions, and any action arising from or related to this Privacy Policy and the use of our Site shall be brought only and exclusively before the courts of Tel Aviv, Israel.

Copyright – All rights reserved. © 2018  
www.eteachergroup.com – eTeacher Ltd.
